"It seems today that all you see
"is violence in movies and sex on TV
"But where are those good,
old-fashioned values
"on which we used to rely?
"Lucky there's a family guy
"Lucky there's a man who'll
positively tell you
"all the things that make us
"laugh 'n' cry
"He's a family guy"
- I'm Morley Safer.
- I'm Mike Wallace.
- I'm Ed Bradley.
- I'm Lesley Stahl.
And one of you is hung like an elf.
I feel so naughty.
Lois, what are you doing?
Neither of us is drunk.
Knock it off!
Oh, my God! I found a lump!
A breast lump!
The important thing is to stay calm.
It's probably nothing, honey.
That's easy for you to say.
You get to keep both your cans.
Peter, don't talk like that!
You'll see a doctor tomorrow and...
No. I'm not gonna see a doctor, Lois.
The healthiest thing we can do is just
ignore this and pretend it doesn't exist.
Just like we do with the squid.
Earthquake.
Truck going by.
I'm gonna be fine.
Nothing to worry about.
Morning.
Give it to me straight, Doc.
How long do I have?
Mr. Griffin, I'd say you have
about a month to live.
But what the hell do I know?
I've been sued by every patient I ever had.
Look at the size of this file.
This is... Wow.
Let's just wait for the test results.
Finish up, honey.
Then I'll put you down for a nice nap.
No! I shall put you down
for a nap, Mother!
Blast!
I'm so worried about your father.
You mean because
he's a borderline alcoholic?
No. Mommy's made peace with that.
Because he's got a lump on his booby.
Chris, that's a terrible word, "booby."
Mom, Debbie Miller's dad had a lump
on his breast, and he turned out okay.
Really? Who's Debbie Miller?
A girl I just made up.
Look. Here they are. My family.
Guys, I don't say this often enough,
but I'm gonna die.
Oh, my God.
High five! Anyone?
Anyone?
You can't die! Who's gonna take me
to the Father-Son dance?
Listen, I've had a good life.
You can always be proud of your father
and all of his accomplishments.
Accomplishments?
Go to your room.
Peter, there's no way you could die.
You're the most important character
in this family.
I'll take this one.
But I won't pay a cent over $60.
Sir, that casket costs $1,000.
Okay, $70.
What?
$2,000.
That's twice the cost!
$40.
What?
He doesn't know how to haggle.
Peter, what's going on?
I'm selling all my worldly goods,
so you'll have some cash when I'm dead.
Yeah, a lot of memories here.
Look, my first bike.
Boy, I had so much fun playing with that.
More tea, Mr. Bike?
Peter, this is ridiculous.
You're going to be fine.
Dad, the doctor called.
Your test results are in.
This doesn't look very good.
No, this doesn't look very good at all.
My nephew drew my portrait.
It doesn't look a thing like me.
Look at the nose. It's all...
Will you just tell us about Peter's tests?
Okay. Mr. Griffin,
all your tests came back negative.
As it turns out, the lump on your chest
was just a fatty corpuscle.
Fatty corpuscle? Wait a minute.
How the hell can a dead comedian...
...from the silent movie era
be lodged in my left bosom?
Mr. Griffin, I'm saying you're fine.
I'm fine? What?
Are you coming on to me now?
Peter, he's not coming on to you.
He's trying to tell you that you're healthy.
Can't it be both?
My sweetie is okay.
Better than okay, Lois.
From now on, I'm gonna appreciate...
...all the little things in life,
like you and the kids.
Is this the price of my bill
or my phone number?
Your phone number.
It's still pretty pricey!
Peter, who cares how much it is?
You've just got the most important
bill of all, a clean bill of health.
Jeez, Lois. How long you been waiting
to crack out that gem?
This sucks, Brian.
Why should I have to pay this?
- There's nothing wrong with me.
- Too bad you're not dying.
Wait a second. That's it!
They can't make a dead guy pay his bill.
All I gotta do is write "deceased"
right here where it says "name."
And where it says "sex,"
I'll write, "No, thanks. I'm dead."
It's bulletproof.
But you promised
the fat one would perish.
I know. Isn't it wonderful, honey?
Your father is alive and well...
...and we can be a family for a good long...
Who are you?
I'm Calista Flockhart. Who the
hell do you think I am? I'm Death.
Which one of you is Peter Griffin?
He is.
Come on, man.
Which one of you is Peter Griffin?
This is Peter Griffin.
That's a good one.
Why are you...
No, wait.
I'm not finished holding my sides.
Why are...
Why...
Why are you here?
The doctor said Peter was okay.
The doctor!
I guess he must know, right?
I mean, he's a doctor and everything,
and I'm just Death!
Excuse me. Hello!
I'm Stewie. Big fan.
Death, you made a mistake.
I'm not supposed to be dead.
I made a mistake? What's this?
Peter, is that your handwriting?
How did you get that?
Your HMO emailed it to me.
I know my doctor was hitting on me,
but you don't have to call him names.
I don't care what that says!
You can't take my husband!
Mother! Where are your manners?
Don't argue with our guest!
Won't you join us for dinner?
Oh, no. I don't want to impose.
Is that turkey?
Yes, Death.
We were in the middle of a turkey dinner
to celebrate Peter's good health.
Do you mind?
Mind? Of course not.
It would be an honor.
No, it would be a privilege. Oh, dear.
Listen to me prattling on like a schoolgirl.
Come, come.
You, heat up some gravy for our guest!
My last helping of white meat
was drier than Oscar Wilde.
How did you do that?
Let's just say,
when I was younger...
...I did some films
I'm not particularly proud of.
That does it for me.
Wait! You can't go.
After dinner,
we usually go into the living room...
...and live for another 40 or 50 years.
40 or... Let's go.
I guess this is good-bye.
Meg, you're the man of the family now.
Be strong.
Daddy.
Stewie, I guess I'm not gonna be here
to see you become a man.
Yes. I think we all know
what that's going to be like.
A 20-minute call to Larchmont?
Who do we know in Larchmont?
My sister-in-law.
Yes, right. Right. Carol. Yes.
That's right. How is Carol?
- Brian.
- Oh, God.
- Daddy, can I come with you?
- Ask your mother.
No, you can't go with him!
- Oh, Peter.
- Lois.
Okay, that's good. Come on now.
Hey, Death, you got a file on me?
Yeah, it's in the car, I think.
Does it mention that I ran two weeks
of Junior Varsity track?
Let's not do this. I caught Flo Jo.
You don't think I can catch you?
My ankle!
Yeah, listen,
don't help or anything. I'm totally fine.
Damn Irish.
Yeah. That felt good,
dropping me on the couch like that.
Here's some Tylenol.
Great. Tylenol. I asked for Advil.
But, you know, whatever. That's good.
I got a B-plus in Health.
Is there anything I can do?
Why don't you boil some water
and rip up some sheets there, Einstein.
It's a sprained ankle.
I have to stay off it for a while.
Not here.
Why?
You tried to kill me!
Besides, how are we supposed
to explain you to Mr. Roper?
It's okay, Death.
You just worry about feeling better.
What the hell are you doing?
Peter, don't you see?
As long as he's here, you can't die.
Go on.
That's it.
Wait a minute.
So no matter what I do, I won't die?
Make yourself at home, Death.
I'm going out for a while.
Wait.
You can't tell anyone I'm here.
For if humanity discovers...
...l'm no longer lurking in the shadows,
consequences will be dire.
Go on.
That's it.
What the hell do you see in him?
Peter, where are you going?
Lois, 10 minutes ago,
I was staring Death in the face.
Now that I've been given another chance...
...l'm gonna do the one thing
I've always dreamed of doing.
I'm gonna jump off this building.
Could you repeat that, please, Peter?
I believe I had something crazy in my ear.
Hold the phone.
You took me away from
a Swedish girlie-girl...
...and her paralyzed,
but trusting, cousin for this?
- $1,000 says I live.
- $1,000, huh?
- What the hell?
- Okay.
Look at that. I beat my loogie.
It's your turn, Death.
I know I should find this ironic,
but I'm just bored as hell.
How old is this TV?
You can probably get
the DuMont Network on this thing.
Peter is a good man
and a wonderful father.
Here it comes.
Could you please find it in your heart
to spare him?
After all, it isn't really his time.
What did you use
for this cocoa, crap?
If you want me to make it again...
Sorry, my fault.
I just assumed you were gonna make it
with milk, not crap!
I'll be right back.
I brought you a magazine.
Glamour, great.
I can learn how to please my man.
Go get me an Entertainment Weekly.
I hear it's got a great picture of me
sneaking up on Tom Snyder.
Victory is mine!
Wow. I should really
watch where I'm going.
What the deuce?
Of course!
It seems with Death incapacitated,
my matricidal efforts are futile.
I must do all I can to accelerate
his convalescence.
"Knick-knack paddywhack,
give a dog a bone"
I can't believe you drank 300 bottles
of beer without succumbing...
...to alcohol poisoning.
Peter, are you a witch?
Yeah. But don't tell anyone.
The consequences could be dire!
You guys, I bet I can go up to each one
of those scary-looking bikers and say:
"Aren't you Richard Simmons?"
- Peter, no!
- Now you're being brainless.
Aren't you Richard Simmons?
Aren't you Richard Simmons' best friend,
Richard Simmons?
Shut up!
That feels good.
Actually, kid, I kind of fell into this gig.
I really wanted to be a wood nymph.
Man, the second Dad found out,
he started in with the whole:
"I have no son. I have no son,"
and Mom just stood there.
Yes. Mothers can be quite
the botheration, can't they?
That's why we've got to get you well.
- What was that?
- Nothing!
Stewie, leave Death alone.
He's okay.
He reminds me a lot of me at that age.
I hope his teen years go better than mine.
Boy, talk about awkward.
Oh, Sandy! Sandy!
Sandy? Not again.
I'm gonna be a virgin forever.
Or am I?
Can we please talk about Peter?
He has so much to live for, Death.
He loves his children and me...
Okay. I'll spare his life.
But you owe me, if you get my drift.
What the hell are you doing?
I was talking about another fruit cup.
Not bad, though.
Peter,
Death just agreed to let you live.
Oh, man. This really is my night.
I get to live, and I'm on TV.
Our top story tonight,
the rules of death no longer apply.
That's right, Tom.
Our own Asian reporter, Trisha Takanawa,
filed this report, all by herself!
I'm here with Peter Griffin,
the man who claims he withstood...
...a barrage of bullets and did not die.
Peter, are you saying
that if I shoot you in the head...
...with this Channel 5 pistol,
you'll be completely unharmed?
Why don't you give it a shot?
Okay, here goes.
What have I done?
You're awful.
- Fascinating story, Tom.
- It sure is, Diane.
And since the laws of death
no longer apply, I can do this.
That's right, Tom.
And now it's time for sports.
The whole world is laughing
at me. This is high school all over again.
Well, I'll show them! I'll show all of them!
Oh, my God, that hurts!
You're not killing anyone tonight, mister!
Not on that ankle.
This is all your fault.
And there's only one solution.
You have to go out there and do my job.
You have to be Death!
Boy, this doesn't leave much
to the imagination.
Death, there is no way
Peter can do your job.
He could never kill anyone.
Yeah! I've thought about it,
like in church and stuff...
...but I don't think I could ever do
what you do.
So you're better than me?
I'm tired of always being the bad guy.
What I do has to be done.
He's right. You've disturbed
the natural order.
People need to be able to die.
No!
- Actually, I think I'm gonna be okay.
- Oh, Jack.
Now we can get married
and everything you promised.
Yeah, about that...
...I was pretty sure I was gonna die...
...because there's this girl in New York,
and it's getting kind of serious.
But thanks for letting me draw you naked.
I still can't believe you let me do that!
You're saying the only way to make
the world right is for me to kill someone?
You could kill Lois.
No. One death isn't gonna do it.
You have to do something that will
get everyone's attention, something huge.
How about if you blow up the earth?
Too huge.
But you're thinking. I like that.
You could kill any girls
who are prettier than me.
That would just leave England.
Wait. I have it.
I'm a genius.
You'll kill the kids from Dawson's Creek!
I knew it! As soon as that show
came on the air, I said:
"I'm gonna be the one
who has to kill these kids."
It's true. He did say it.
Hot, young celebrities.
It's perfect!
The kids are on their way to LA
to renegotiate their contracts.
But their plane is gonna be making
a little stopover in Rhode Island.
If you go now, you'll catch them.
No way.
I'm not doing your dirty work.
There's no way I'm getting on that plane.
Absolutely no way, and that's final.
See? I'm still here.
There's nothing you can say
that'll change my mind.
You kill them, or I kill you.
Crap!
Nice plant.
Note to self, do not go to the bathroom.
James,
your last movie killed at the box office.
Your Q-rating's through the roof.
It's time we ditched the WB
and concentrate on features.
I don't know who you are,
but just because you're sitting...
...across from me doesn't mean
you can give me career advice.
- Will you sign my ass?
- You have a pen?
Hello, Death?
Guess where I'm calling from?
A plane!
That's great.
Are those kids on board?
Yeah.
About that,
I don't think I can go through with it.
Peter, listen, without death,
the world would be a terrible place.
Imagine a world
where Hitler was still alive.
Today on Hitler,
we'll be talking with Christian Slater.
Now, they tell me in your next movie,
we get to see your butt.
Yes, you do.
Can we see it right now?
All right.
He's going to do it!
If you're going to be in L.A.
And would like tickets to Hitler...
...call 213-du werdest
eine Krankenschwester brauchen!
Peter, all you gotta do is sit there.
The plane is gonna crash in LA.
Pilot error. Big mess. Everybody dies.
Jeez, everybody?
Except you.
Hold on, I'm getting another call. Brenda?
It's still me.
Brenda?
Yes? Just kidding, it's still me.
We now begin our final approach
into Los Angeles International.
If you look out the window,
you'll see the San Fernando Valley...
...where my brother Gary makes
a very nice living directing porn.
We'll be on the ground in 10 minutes.
"We like being alive,
we like being alive
"We like being, oh, we like being,
oh, we like being alive"
I guess it's their time.
Boy, for a teacher,
you sure make love good.
Actually, it's "well," Pacey.
You mean to say, I make love "well."
- You're good to go again, right?
- Yeah.
Peter? Hello? Peter,
are you there? I can hear you breathing?
Yeah, I'm here. And you can forget it.
I've changed my mind.
I don't care if you do kill me,
I'm not gonna kill those kids.
If they die, I'll have nothing
to watch on Wednesdays...
...other than the fine programs on Fox.
Open up in there!
What are you doing? You're not a pilot.
I know every pilot in the world!
I'm here to keep you from making an error.
A pilot error.
Jeez, I probably should've worn mittens!
Nice going, fat...
I was just trying to save your lives.
But now you're all gonna die.
- No one can land this plane.
- I can.
Thank God! It's Karen Black!
She landed a busted plane in Airport '75?
It was a movie in the '70s.
You damn kids with your music.
Both of the pilots were killed.
Fortunately for the other passengers,
actress Karen Black...
...star of such films as Nashville
and Five Easy Pieces, was on board.
Hats off to Miss Black for proving
once again that, given the opportunity...
...actresses over 50 can land large aircraft.
Karen Black. What an obscure reference!
What the hell? I told you to waste
the Dawson's Creek kids.
You're missing
the important thing here.
You said you wanted everyone to know
the rules of death apply.
Now the whole world does.
I guess so.
My ankle's starting to feel better.
I should probably get out of your hair.
But you just got here!
We can stay in touch, can't we?
What's your e-mail?
Mine is "loismustdie," all one word,
"@yahoo.com."
Wait a second. Death?
I used to fear you,
but now I'm glad we met.
Because you've given me a great gift.
The complete Boz Scaggs.
How did you know?
I just had a feeling.
We're gonna miss you, Death.
Don't worry.
I'll be back really, really soon.
Is he joking?
Okay, see you later.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru